<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts on Gandes Goldestan</title>
    <link>https://gandesgold.github.io/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thoughts on Gandes Goldestan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gandesgold.github.io/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Relationship Doesn&#39;t Mean to Make Us Happy, But It Makes Us Conscious</title>
      <link>https://gandesgold.github.io/thoughts/relationship-doesnt-mean-to-make-us-happy-but-it-makes-us-conscious/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gandesgold.github.io/thoughts/relationship-doesnt-mean-to-make-us-happy-but-it-makes-us-conscious/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;When you blame and criticize others, you are avoiding some truth about yourself.&amp;quot; — Deepak Chopra
 As a human being I believe that each of us must has experienced problems with others, whether it&amp;rsquo;s with our parents, siblings, lovers, friends, and so on. And as humans, almost all of us must have felt irritated and blamed them in the end, right? Well, by writing this post actually it doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that I want to be seen as a philosopher, wise person, or whatever it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Having Side Project? Why Not?</title>
      <link>https://gandesgold.github.io/thoughts/having-side-project-why-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gandesgold.github.io/thoughts/having-side-project-why-not/</guid>
      <description>Hi again, folks!
In my previous blog post I have written about my experience and benefits I got from having a bookstagram account. After launched my bookstagram, I promoted it to my friends firstly, including my work colleagues. One of them was even saying, “Wow, this is great! I like seeing people who have side project to do.”
Oh, &amp;ldquo;side project&amp;rdquo;?
Well, actually ‘side project’ are common words. But I don’t know why, it feels like this word caught my attention suddenly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefits I Get from Managing a Bookstagram</title>
      <link>https://gandesgold.github.io/thoughts/benefits-i-get-from-managing-a-bookstagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gandesgold.github.io/thoughts/benefits-i-get-from-managing-a-bookstagram/</guid>
      <description>Hi, this is my first writing in my blog site, and I am going to share about the experience and benefits I get from having a bookstagram.
One day a friend who is also my work colleague chatted me suddenly. She told me that she just bought a Kindle like mine from an online marketplace. Yeah Kindle, an e-reader device that is usually used by people to read e-books. She said she was thinking to buy it because she doesn’t know what to do to spend her leisure time in this Corona pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>